https://alveyssigns.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Who we are
Our website address is: https://alveyssigns.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Who we share your data with
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
Additional information
How we protect your data
What data breach procedures we have in place
What third parties we receive data from
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
Alvey's Sign Company
Prokuma, Inc.Alvey Signs designed and created an awesome, illuminated sign that fit our budget and delivery needs perfectly. Madeline and her… More» “Prokuma, Inc.”Prokuma, Inc.Craig A. Weinzapfel, P.E. - Electrical and Controls EngineerMore Testimonials»Daisy’s Pet PlaygroundAlvey was great to work with from the initial sales call, design and through installation. Having worked with other area… More» “Daisy’s Pet Playground”Daisy’s Pet PlaygroundMark JewellMore Testimonials»Integrated ImageAlveys is a reliable sign manufacturer. They turn around estimates quickly, send production updates, and keep to their schedules/expectations. If… More» “Integrated Image”More Testimonials»MH EquipmentOur new signs are up and they look great! We appreciate your diligence and professionalism as we worked to get… More» “MH Equipment”MH EquipmentMike Goebel - President - South/East RegionMore Testimonials»Garmong ConstructionOur new sign is awesome! We are receiving lots of great compliments from our clients weekly. I’ve even had people… More» “Garmong Construction”Garmong ConstructionEvie BaldwinMore Testimonials»Sweet Betty’s BakeryWe are so happy that Alvey’s could make our sign look better than ever. Not only is their work beautiful,… More» “Sweet Betty’s Bakery”Sweet Betty's BakeryAndrea MilesMore Testimonials»Polen’s Buy It Rite Auto SalesA big thank you to you and your team for the great sign for our dealership. We are so very… More» “Polen’s Buy It Rite Auto Sales”Polen's Buy It Rite Auto SalesRandy and Felicia PolenMore Testimonials»Hafer Design – Evansville Regional AirportAlvey’s Signs was a true creative collaborator that brought passion and expertise to the design process. The end result was… More» “Hafer Design – Evansville Regional Airport”Hafer DesignJason Barisano, AIA, LEED APMore Testimonials»Evansville Print SpecialistsAlvey’s Signs, a quick shout out to your team, from your sales rep, pre-press & install teams, we were treated… More» “Evansville Print Specialists”Evansville Print SpecialistsButch Frank - PresidentMore Testimonials»Hipp DentistryI chose Alvey’s for a new sign on my dental office. From the sales staff to to the install, the… More» “Hipp Dentistry”Hipp DentistryEvan Hipp DMD More Testimonials»WNIN – EvansvilleWe enjoyed working with Alvey Signs for our new WNIN Public Media Center signage. Madeline’s professional manner and attention to… More» “WNIN – Evansville”WNIN - EvansvilleCarlinMore Testimonials»The Glass FactoryThank you so much! So many compliments and lots of business owners asking who made it. Sending them your… More» “The Glass Factory”The Glass FactoryMore Testimonials»Owensboro-Daviess County Regional Airport (OWB)Alvey’s Signs was an integral partner in every phase of making the Owensboro-Daviess County Regional Airport’s vision come to life.… More» “Owensboro-Daviess County Regional Airport (OWB)”Owensboro-Daviess County Regional Airport (OWB)Tristan Durban - Operations ManagerMore Testimonials»
